<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder 
  xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
  xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">

	<g:HTMLPanel>
<!-- Header -->
<div id="hdr">
<div style="font-weight:bold;font-size:12px;margin:6px 10px;">
Link 1 | Link 2 | Link 3 | Link 4</div>
</div>
<!-- left column -->
<div id="lh-col"><br />
<h4 align="center">Left Column</h4>
<p align="center">The left col can be used for navigation links,
search box etc.</p>
<br />
<br />
<p align="center"><a
href="http://www.ssi-developer.net/main/templates/">View more
templates.</a></p>
</div>
<!-- end of left column -->
<!-- right column -->
<div id="rh-col">
<p align="center"><a href="http://www.ssi-developer.net/"
title="Go to main page."><img src="logo.gif" alt="" border="0"
width="230" height="50" /></a></p>
<h3 align="center">Two Column - Left Column Static with Header
Bar</h3>
<div align="center" style="color: red;">Ver 2.3</div>
<p>The left column is absolutly positioned and is a fixed width.
It won't move.</p>
<p>The header row and content column, which you are reading from,
are flexible. They will automatically change shape, width can be
controlled by setting appropriate margins or an actual width can
be specified if required.</p>
<p>This template has been tested in:</p>
<ul>
<li>Mozilla 1.5b &amp; Firebird 0.6.1</li>
<li>Internet Explorer 6</li>
<li>Netscape 7.1</li>
<li>Opera 7.11</li>
</ul>
<p>Changes in this version:</p>
<ol>
<li>Defined zero for the body to fix a problem in Opera.</li>
</ol>
<br />
<p style="font-weight: bold;">Filler Content</p>
<p lang="ga">Dzig alta in mac sin i tig a athar &amp; a mathar
icon airdig i m-Maig Muirthemne, ocus adfeta dz sczla na maccaemi
i n-Emain. Dzig is amlaid domeill Conchobar in rigi, o ro gab
rzgi in rz, .i. mar atraig fzchetzir czsta &amp; cangni in
choicid d'ordugud. In lz do raind i trz asa athlil: cetna trian
de fzchetzir ic fegad na maccaem ic imbirt chless cluchi &amp;
immanae, in trian tanaise dond lz ic imbirt brandub &amp;
fidchell, &amp; in trian dedenach ic tochathim bzd &amp; lenna,
con-dageib cotlud for czch, aes czuil &amp; airfitid dia thalgud
fri sodain. Ciataim ane ar longais riam reme dabiur brzthir, ar
Fergus, na fuil in hErind no i n-Albain zclach macsamla
Conchobair.</p>
<p lang="ga">Ocus adfeta don mac sin sczla na macezem &amp; na
maccraide i n-Emain, &amp; radis in mac bec ria mathair ar co
n-digsed dz chluchi do chluchemaig na Emna. Romoch duitsiu sain a
meic bic, ar a mathair, co n-deoch anruth do anrothaib. Ulad lett
no choimthecht ecin do chaimthechtaib Conchobair, do chor th'
aesma &amp; t'imdegla for in maccraid. Czan lim-sa di sodain a
mathair, ar in mac bec, &amp; ni biu-sa oca idnaide acht
tecoisc-siu dam-sa cia airm itz Emain. Is czan uait, ar a
mathair, airm in-das-fil. Sliab Fzait etrut &amp; Emain. Dobzr-sa
ardmes furri amne, ar esium.</p>
</div>
<!-- end of right column -->

	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>